<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Geopedia</string>
    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_map">Map</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Bookmarks</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="sarstring">A limitation of optical satellite remote sensing is that it depends on cloudless, well-illuminated areas to produce quality data. This is especially problematic for collecting data during nighttime, around storms, and in densely-forested areas. Synthetic Aperture Radar (SAR) is a solution for many of these obstacles. SAR can observe the Earth\'s surface day and night, through most weather conditions, and the signal can penetrate the vegetation canopy.</string>
    <string name="Ladsweb">LAADS DAAC primarily archives and distributes data on clouds, water vapor, and aerosols in Earth’s atmosphere as well as key instrument data for NASA, NOAA and European Space Administration missions. LAADS DAAC also serves as a backup source for MODIS and VIIRS land products.</string>
    <string name="HLSstring">NASA\'s Land Processes Distributed Active Archive Center (LP DAAC) archives and distributes HLS products in the LP DAAC Cumulus cloud archive as Cloud Optimized GeoTIFFs (COG). This tutorial will demonstrate how to query and subset HLS data using the NASA Common Metadata Repository (CMR) SpatioTemporal Asset Catalog (STAC). Because these data are stored as COGs, this tutorial will teach users how to load subsets of individual files into memory for just the bands you are interested in--a paradigm shift from the more common workflow where you would need to download a .zip/HDF file containing every band over the entire scene/tile.</string>
    <string name="gracestring">GRACE measured gravity by relating it to the distance between the twin satellites. When there was an increase in gravity ahead of the pair, the front satellite sped up and the distance between the pair increased. When there was an increase in gravity between the pair their distance decreased. The opposite occurred when there was decreased gravity ahead of, or between the satellite pair. The satellites were separated by 220 km and could detect changes smaller than a micrometer per second in relative velocity.</string>
    <string name="laadsstring"><![CDATA[\nLevel-0 / Level-1 [40]\nMODIS Terra, Aqua [14]\nVIIRS Suomi NPP [15]\nOLCI ESA Copernicus Sentinel-3A [2]\nSLSTR ESA Copernicus Sentinel-3A [1]\nOLCI ESA Copernicus Sentinel-3B [2]\nSLSTR ESA Copernicus Sentinel-3B [1]\nMERIS Envisat [5]\nAtmosphere [52]\nAerosol [12]\nWater Vapor [5]\nCloud Properties [14]\nAtmosphere Profiles [4]\nCloud Mask [5]\nL2 Joint Atmosphere Product [2]\nL3 Atmosphere Product [8]\nVIIRS+CrIS Fusion [2]\nLand [156]\nRadiation Budget Variables [117]\nLand Surface Reflectance [22]\nLand Surface Temperature & Emissivity [18]\nBRDF & Albedo [77]\nEcosystem Variables [24]\nVegetation Indices [12]\nLAI & fPAR [6]\nGPP & NPP [6]\nLand Cover Characteristics [15]\nThermal Anomalies & Fire [6]\nBurned Area [1]\nLand Cover [3]\nVegetation Continuous Fields [1]\nNighttime Lights [4]\nNACP Gap Filled Smoothed [10]\nLAI & fPAR [2]\nEnhanced Vegetation Index (EVI) [4]\nNormalized Difference Vegetation Index (NDVI) [4]\nOther [252]\n]]></string>
    <string name="NasaEarth">This is an official website for the availability of all the imagery alongwith other data captured over time by satellites of nasa.</string>
    <string name="emitstring">Mineral dust blown into the air is an important part of the Earth system.  Wind blows dust into the atmosphere from desert regions around the world, and can carry dust across oceans. Dark minerals that absorb sunlight can warm the Earth, while light-colored minerals can cool the Earth. By accurately mapping the composition of areas that produce mineral dust, EMIT will advance our understanding of dust’s effects throughout the Earth system and to human populations now and in the future.</string>
</resources>